# Angelos Athanasakos

WEB DEVELOPER

Edinburgh, United Kingdom +44 07472869292, athanasakosangelos@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/angelos-athanasakos-838677109/

https://gitlab.com/athanasakosang elos

## **PROFILE**

A highly-motivated 3rd year student with already one year professional experience in web technologies as well as in various personal projects. Competent, quick learner, loves web-tech stuff and enjoys an occasional gif (or cats?) exchange with fellow like-minded colleagues.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

# UNIVERSITY OF EDINBURGH | CMS SUPPORT ASSISTANT | 2016 - 2017

- Provided 1st/2nd line support.
- Responsible for delivering front-end and back-end enhancements to the University website as well as relevant web applications.
- Support and development of UoE Docker application.
- User acceptance testing for new website features.

### IBIS | FOOD & BEVERAGE TEAM MEMBER | 2014 - 2016

- Responsible for welcoming guests and ensuring the smooth operation of breakfast.
- Coordinator of the evening floor team when requested including groups management for the best restaurant performance.
- Helped with coming up with new products and improving the customer experience.

## **EDUCATION**

# EDINBURGH NAPIER UNIVERITY | BSC WEB DESIGN AND DEVELOPMENT | 2014-2018

Software development.
Web technologies.
Advanced web technologies.
Software engineering methods.

Database systems. Human computer interaction User centred design Digital storytelling

## SKILLS OVERVIEW

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Strong Analytical problem-solving skills.
Strong Communication skills.
Multilingual (Greek, English, French, Italian).
Ability to research, absorb and analyze highly technical. information quickly and efficiently.

#### **HARD SKILLS**

- Experience with configuring Webservers (LAMP, WAMP, MAMP) as well as utilizing Docker and Vagrant capabilities to release development environments which allows the quick Dockerisation and deployment of applications.
- Highly proficient of the Drupal 7 framework including Drupal coding standards. Also excellent knowledge of Wordpress framework. Extensive knowledge of module development, Drupal theming and site building using a wide range of Drupal modules.
- Experience front end Web Technologies (HTML, CSS, PHP BOOTSTRAP, JQUERY, Python, SQL) for designing and developing websites. Good Exposure to UX and Accessibility guidelines and user centred design.
- Experience with testing applications and carrying out formal User Acceptance Tests.
- Proficient using version control software (Git).
- Experience working with Agile development practices.

### **ACHIEVEMENTS, PROJECTS & INTERESTS**

# UNIVERSITY OF EDINBURGH

www.gel.ed.ac.uk & www.ed.ac.uk enchantements,
Development of UoE Docker & Editor's time log,
Active contributor to UoE Git repository,
Front end development of http://edinburgh-uk.libguides.com

# PERSONAL ACHIEVEMENTS

Developer of www.vzervo.eu, Numerous successful University coursework's and on track for 1:1 degree,

#### **INTERESTS**

Travelling, languages, running, football, photography, reading, cinema